Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - F
        - Fredrix, Randy - The hunter, 1983; SR-15867; Fredrix, Randy (Box 270)
          Catalog # SG 413 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-413-A-1
        - Free - Best of free, 1974; SR-15868; Free (Box 270)
          Catalog # SP-3663; A-side Matrix # A&M SP3663-M1
        - Free Movement - I've found someone of my own, 1972; SR-15869; Free Movement (Box 270)
          Catalog # KC 31136; A-side Matrix # PAL 311336-1C
        - Free Style - No, no, no, my friend (You're wrong so do it again), 1977; SR-15870; Free Style (Box 270)
          Catalog # AVID-12-152; A-side Matrix # 007-12152 SIDEA
          AVI Records
        - Freedom - Whodat, 1982; SR-15871; Freedom (Box 270)
          Catalog # MAL-1207; A-side Matrix # MAL 1207A-2A
          Malaco Records
          Jackson, Mississippi
        - Freedom of Soul - Caught in a land of time, 1991; SR-15872; Freedom of Soul (Box 270)
          Catalog # E 47801; A-side Matrix # BL47801-1A
        - Freeland, Adam - On tour sampler, 2001; SR-15873; Freeland, Adam (Box 270)
          Catalog # 67728-54697-1; A-side Matrix # MAPA VLP 02 A1
          Kinetic Records
        - Freeman, Louise - Signed sealed delivered, 1987; SR-15874; Freeman, Louise; Blount, Terry (Box 270)
          Catalog # STTL 714; A-side Matrix # ST-714-A-1
          Suntown Records
        - Freeman, Michele - Tumble heat, 1979; SR-15875; Freeman, Michele (Box 270)
          Catalog # PD D 514; A-side Matrix # PDD-514-70-NP-4338-S-RE-CP-1
        - Freestyle Fellowship - Bullies of the block, 1992; SR-15876; Freestyle Fellowship (Box 270)
          Catalog # 162 440 562-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-562-1-AS/SP
          4th & Broadway
        - Freestylers - Raw as f**k (Disc one), 2004; SR-15877; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15878 and SR-15879. Triple album. Annotated.
          Catalog # ATGLP01; A-side Matrix # DF103-6 ATGLP01-A-
          Against The Grain
        - Freestylers - Raw as f**k (Disc two), 2004; SR-15878; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15877 and SR-15879. Triple album. Annotated.
          Catalog # ATGLP01; A-side Matrix # DF103-6 ATGLP01-C-
        - Freestylers - Raw as f**k (Disc three), 2004; SR-15879; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15877 and SR-15878. Triple album. Annotated.
          Catalog # ATGLP01; A-side Matrix # DF103-6 ATGLP01-E-
        - Freestylers - Push up (Remixes), 2004; SR-15880; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15881. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ATG009R; A-side Matrix # ATG 009RA
        - Freestylers - Push up (Remixes), 2004; SR-15881; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15880. 2 copies.
        - Freestylers - Warning, 1998; SR-15882; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15883. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FNT14; A-side Matrix # FNT-14 A
          Freskanova
        - Freestylers - Warning, 1998; SR-15883; Freestylers (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15882. 2 copies.
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1982; SR-15884; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15885. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SWRL 2210; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2210-A
          Streetwise
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1982; SR-15885; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15884. 2 copies.
        - Freeez - Southern Freeez, 1981; SR-15886; Freeez (Box 270)
          Catalog # 151.041; A-side Matrix # 151.041-A1
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1982; SR-15887; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15888. 2 copies.
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1982; SR-15888; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15887. 2 copies.
        - Freeez - Pop goes my love, 1983; SR-15889; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15890. Different discs.
          Catalog # BEG 98; A-side Matrix # BEG 98T A-1U-1-1-1
        - Freeez - Pop goes my love, 1983; SR-15890; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15889. Different discs.
          Catalog # SWRL-2215; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2215-A
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1983; SR-15891; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15892. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BEG 96; A-side Matrix # BEG-96-T-A-1U-1-2
        - Freeez - I.O.U., 1983; SR-15892; Freeez (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15891. 2 copies.
        - Freeze - Freeze, 1991; SR-15893; Freeze (Box 270)
          Catalog # PRO-1412A-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-1412-A
        - Freeze Factor - Lay back and chill, 1988; SR-15894; Freeze Factor (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15895. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49 07579; A-side Matrix # XSS 07579A-1A
        - Freeze Factor - Lay back and chill, 1988; SR-15895; Freeze Factor (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15894. 2 copies.
        - French Kiss - Panic; Save me (Suite), 1979; SR-15896; French Kiss (Box 270)
          Catalog # PRO 094; A-side Matrix # PRO-094-79-NP-4117-S-GD
        - Freq Nasty - Boomin' back atcha, 1999; SR-15897; Freq Nasty; Phoebe One (Box 270)
          Catalog # BOS2022; A-side Matrix # BOS-2022 A-1
          Botchit & Scarper
        - Fresh 3 M.C.'s - Have your heart; A few minutes more, 1984; SR-15898; Fresh 3 M.C.'s (Box 270)
          Catalog # PRO-7055-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7055-A
        - Fresh 4 - Wishing on a star, 1989; SR-15899; Fresh 4 (Box 270)
          Catalog # 0-96510; A-side Matrix # STDM 579195792557920-1
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Fresh, Doug E. - The world's greatest entertainer, 1988; SR-15900; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15901. 2 copies.
          Catalog # F-9658; A-side Matrix # F 96587-A
          Reality
          Jersey City, New Jersey
        - Fresh, Doug E. - The world's greatest entertainer, 1988; SR-15901; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # SR-15900. 2 copies.
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Keep risin' to the top; Guess who?, 1988; SR-15902; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          Catalog # D-3101; A-side Matrix # D-3101 A1
        - Fresh, Doug E. - All the way to heaven, 1986; SR-15903; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          Catalog # D-264; A-side Matrix # D-264-A
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Summertime, 1989; SR-15904; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15905. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DR-2701; A-side Matrix # DR2701A
          Walnut Creek, California
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Summertime, 1989; SR-15905; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15904. 2 copies.
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Hands in the air, 1995; SR-15906; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15907. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR 12 7126-1WT; A-side Matrix # PR12-7126-1-A
          Gee Street Independent
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Hands in the air, 1995; SR-15907; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15906. 2 copies.
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Who run this, SR-15908; Fresh, Doug E.; Busy Bee; Luv Bug Starski (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15909. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WRT-001; A-side Matrix # WRT-001 A
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Who run this, SR-15909; Fresh, Doug E.; Busy Bee; Luv Bug Starski (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15908. 2 copies.
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (untitled), 1996; SR-15910; Fresh, Doug E.; Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          Catalog # PHC 1425; A-side Matrix # PHC-1425-A
          Phat Classics
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Play, 1995; SR-15911; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          Catalog # 162-444 069-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-444-069-1-AS/HS
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Freak it out, 1996; SR-15912; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15913. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR12 7211-1WT/AS; A-side Matrix # PR12-7211-A-SP
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Freak it out, 1996; SR-15913; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15912. 2 copies.
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Play, 1995; SR-15914; Fresh, Doug E. (Box 271)
          Catalog # 162-444 069-1; A-side Matrix # 162-444-069-AS/HS
        - Fresh, Doug E. - Bustin' out (On funk), 1992; SR-15915; Fresh, Doug E.; New Get Fresh Crew; Doug E. Fresh and the New Get Fresh Crew (Box 271)
          Catalog # VNR 15822; A-side Matrix # 1-15822-22
          Bust It Records
        - Fresh Force Crew - Rock me, 1986; SR-15916; Fresh Force Crew (Box 271)
          Catalog # SUD 046DJ; A-side Matrix # SUD-046-A
        - Fresh, Freddy - B-Boy stance (Original old skool party rockers) (Disc one), 2002; SR-15917; Fresh, Freddy (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15918. Double album.
          Catalog # STRUTLP 012; A-side Matrix # STRUTLP012-A-1
          Strut
        - Fresh, Freddy - B-Boy stance (Original old skool party rockers) (Disc two), 2002; SR-15918; Fresh, Freddy (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15917. Double album.
          Catalog # STRUTLP 012; A-side Matrix # STRUTLP012C-1
        - Fresh, Freddy - It's about the groove, 1998; SR-15919; Fresh, Freddy (Box 271)
          Catalog # EYE UK 033; A-side Matrix # EYEUK 033-01-1-1
          Eye Q (UK)
        - Fresh, Freddy - Chupacabbra, 1997; SR-15920; Fresh, Freddy (Box 271)
          Catalog # HH 112; A-side Matrix # HH-112-A
          Harthouse
        - Fresh Gordon - Feelin' James, 1987; SR-15921; Fresh Gordon (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15922. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 901; A-side Matrix # TB-901-A
        - Fresh Gordon - Feelin' James, 1987; SR-15922; Fresh Gordon (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15921. 2 copies.
        - Fresh Gordon - Feelin' James, 1987; SR-15923; Fresh Gordon (Box 271)
        - Fresh Kid Ice - Freak 'em down, 1992; SR-15924; Fresh Kid Ice (Box 271)
          Catalog # PR-221; A-side Matrix # ST-E-730-B-2
          Effect Records
          Liberty City, Florida
        - Fresh Ski & Mo Rock - Talking pays, 1989; SR-15925; Fresh Ski & Mo Rock (Box 271)
          Catalog # TUFF 003; A-side Matrix # TUFF-003-A
          Tuff Groove
        - Freshmäka - La la la, 2000; SR-15926; Freshmäka (Box 271)
          Catalog # MM 88469-1; A-side Matrix # 88469-1A
          Moonshine Music
          West Hollywood, California
        - Freshmäka - La la la, 1999; SR-15927; Freshmäka (Box 271)
          Catalog # MM 88467-1; A-side Matrix # MM 88467-1A
        - Freshmen - Who me?, 1986; SR-15928; Freshmen (Box 271)
          Catalog # FMS 62270; A-side Matrix # FMS 62270
        - Fretton, Matt - Dance it up, 1983; SR-15929; Fretton, Matt (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15930. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MATTX 2; A-side Matrix # MATTX 2 A//2
        - Fretton, Matt - Dance it up, 1983; SR-15930; Fretton, Matt (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15929. 2 copies.
        - Freur - Doot-doot, 1983; SR-15931; Freur (Box 271)
          Catalog # 49-03910; A-side Matrix # XSS-17094-1A
        - Friday, Gavin - You me and World War III, 1996; SR-15932; Friday, Gavin (Box 271)
          Catalog # PR12 7149-1WT/BS; A-side Matrix # PR12-714 9-1 AS-HS
        - Friends of Earth - Friend or foe?, 1985; SR-15933; Friends of Earth (Box 271)
          Catalog # 18NS-1006; A-side Matrix # AW 19 X1
          Non-Standard
        - Fringe - Hey, open up!, 1983; SR-15934; Fringe (Box 271)
          Catalog # AGG-003; A-side Matrix # AGG-003 A
          Ap-Gu-Ga Records
          Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts
        - Fronde - L'âme de fond, 1998; SR-15935; Fronde (Box 271)
          Catalog # LP001; A-side Matrix # LP 001-A-
          La Plèbe Productions
        - Front 242 - Politics of pressure, 1988; SR-15936; Front 242 (Box 271)
          Catalog # WAX 014; A-side Matrix # WAX014A
          Wax Trax! Records
        - Front 242 - No comment, 1987; SR-15937; Front 242 (Box 271)
          Catalog # WAX 010; A-side Matrix # WAX-010-A
        - Front BC - Friendly fire, 1999; SR-15938; Front BC (Box 271)
          Catalog # COA 77146; A-side Matrix # COA-77146-A S-40366
          City of Angels
        - First Choice - California style; Doctor love, SR-15939; First Choice; Grant, Eddy (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15940. 2 copies.
          Catalog # RP 013; A-side Matrix # RP013A
          RP Records, Inc.
        - First Choice - California style; Doctor love, SR-15940; First Choice; Grant, Eddy (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15939. 2 copies.
        - Front Page - Love insurance, 1979; SR-15941; Front Page (Box 271)
          Catalog # JD-11677; A-side Matrix # YD-11677A-1
          Panorama Records
        - Front Page - Come to poppa, 1994; SR-15942; Front Page (Box 271)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3011; A-side Matrix # MCA 11997 PDS-2
        - Frost - East Side Rendezvous, 1995; SR-15943; Frost; Kid Frost (Box 271)
          Catalog # 88561-1534-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1534-1 A
        - Frost - La raza II, 1996; SR-15944; Frost; Kid Frost (Box 271)
          Catalog # 88561-1556-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-1556-1 A
        - Frosty - I need llove now, 1987; SR-15945; Frosty (Box 271)
          Catalog # TB 906; A-side Matrix # TB-906-A
        - Fu-Schnickens - Sum dum munkey; Visions (20/20), 1994; SR-15946; Fu-Schnickens (Box 271)
          Catalog # JDCB-42276-1; A-side Matrix # JDCB42276-1-B-1
        - Fu-Schnickens - Sum dum munkey; Visions (20/20), 1994; SR-15947; Fu-Schnickens (Box 271)
          Catalog # JDCB-42276-1; A-side Matrix # JDCB42276-1-C-1
        - Fu-Schnickens - Heavenly father, 1992; SR-15948; Fu-Schnickens (Box 271)
          Catalog # JIVE T 315; A-side Matrix # JIVE T 315 A 2
        - Fudge - Chronic irresponsibility (Disc one), 2001; SR-15949; Fudge (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15950. Double album.
          Catalog # SS-002; A-side Matrix # SS-002 A
          SureShot Entertainments
          Nottingham, England
        - Fudge - Chronic irresponsibility (Disc two), 2001; SR-15950; Fudge (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15949. Double album.
          Catalog # SS-002; A-side Matrix # SS-002 C
        - Fugatives From Hell - Biz with the skillz, 1993; SR-15951; Fugatives From Hell (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15952. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 37789; A-side Matrix # 37789 SIDE-A
          Finesse Records
          Indianapolis, Indiana
        - Fugatives From Hell - Biz with the skillz, 1993; SR-15952; Fugatives From Hell (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15951. 2 copies.
        - Fugatives From Hell - Biz with the skillz, 1993; SR-15953; Fugatives From Hell (Box 271)
        - Fugees - Blunted on reality, 1994; SR-15954; Fugees; Fugees (Tranzlator Crew) (Box 271)
          Catalog # C 57462; A-side Matrix # AL 57462-1A
        - Fugees - Fu-Gee-La, 1995; SR-15955; Fugees; Fugees (Refugee Camp) (Box 271)
          Catalog # 44 78194; A-side Matrix # XSS-78194-A-1A
        - Fugitive - Danger-danger, 1994; SR-15956; Fugitive (Box 271)
          Catalog # CBW-1201; A-side Matrix # CBW-1201-A-
          CBW Records
        - Fugees - Boof baf, 1993; SR-15957; Fugees; Fugees (Tranzlator Crew) (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15958. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 44 77149; A-side Matrix # XSS-77149-A
        - Fugees - Boof baf, 1993; SR-15958; Fugees; Fugees (Tranzlator Crew) (Box 271)
          In same jacket as # SR-15957. 2 copies.
        - Fugees - Nappy heads, 1994; SR-15959; Fugees; Fugees (Tranzlator Crew) (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44 77431; A-side Matrix # XSS-77431-A
        - Fugees - The score (Disc one), 1996; SR-15960; Fugees (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15961. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67147; A-side Matrix # AL 67551-2A
        - Fugees - The score (Disc two), 1996; SR-15961; Fugees (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15960. Double album.
          Catalog # C2 67147; A-side Matrix # AL 67552-2A
        - Full Circle - Workin' up a sweat, 1986; SR-15962; Full Circle (Box 272)
          Catalog # V-19211; A-side Matrix # V-1-19211-Z1
        - Full Force - Girl if you take me home, 1985; SR-15963; Full Force (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44 05232; A-side Matrix # XSS-174405-1A
        - Full Force - Unfaithful so much, 1986; SR-15964; Full Force (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15965. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # 12CXP 05955; A-side Matrix # XSS-175414-1A
        - Full Force - Unfaithful so much, 1986; SR-15965; Full Force (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15964. 2 copies.
        - Full Force - Your love is so def, 1987; SR-15966; Full Force (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44 07828; A-side Matrix # XSS-177828-1B
        - Full Force - Old flames never die, 1987; SR-15967; Full Force (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44 05998; A-side Matrix # XSS-175646-1B
        - Full Force - Unselfish lover, 1986; SR-15968; Full Force (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44-05333; A-side Matrix # XSS-174899-1A
        - Full Force - Your love is so def, 1987; SR-15969; Full Force (Box 272)
          Catalog # 44 07828; A-side Matrix # XSS-177829-1A
        - Full House - I remember, 1987; SR-15970; Full House (Box 272)
          Catalog # DJ 950; A-side Matrix # DJ-950-A
          D.J. International Records
        - Full House - Communicate, 1986; SR-15971; Full House (Box 272)
          Catalog # DJ 926; A-side Matrix # DJ-926-A
        - Full Intention - The return of Full Intention - America; Holdin, 1996; SR-15972; Full Intention (Box 272)
          Catalog # SDR-004; A-side Matrix # SDR-004-A
          Sugar Daddy Records
        - Full Power - Final countdown (Leaving forever), 1995; SR-15973; Full Power (Box 272)
          Catalog # FULL 1; A-side Matrix # FULL 1A
          FBI Records
        - Fun Boy Three - It aint what you do….; Just do it, 1982; SR-15974; Fun Boy Three; Bananarama (Box 272)
          Catalog # CDS 2570; A-side Matrix # CDS-2570-AS PRC-A1-1
        - Fun City - Padentro, 1996; SR-15975; Fun City (Box 272)
          Catalog # CR-367; A-side Matrix # CR-367-A
        - Fun Factory - Close to you, 1994; SR-15976; Fun Factory (Box 272)
          Catalog # YNR-77077; A-side Matrix # YNR 77077-A
          Curb Edel Records
        - Funk Como Le Gusta - Funk Como Le Gusta, 2001; SR-15977; Funk Como Le Gusta (Box 272)
          Catalog # ST2 LP 2001; A-side Matrix # 1002-53-ST2
          ST2 Records
        - Funk Crew - Move (Gotta move on), 1985; SR-15978; Funk Crew (Box 272)
          Catalog # SG 12811; A-side Matrix # SG-12811-A
          Sunshine Recordings
        - Funk Deluxe - Dance it off, 1984; SR-15979; Funk Deluxe (Box 272)
          Catalog # SG 429 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-429-A-1
        - Funk D'Void - Jack me off, 1995; SR-15980; Funk D'Void (Box 272)
          Catalog # soma 029; A-side Matrix # SOME-29-AA
          Soma Quality Recordings
          Glasgow, United Kingdom
        - Funk Inc. - Acid Inc. (The Best of Funk Inc.), 1988; SR-15981; Funk Inc. (Box 272)
          Catalog # BGP 1011; A-side Matrix # DMC-2718 A-1/5-88 CII
          BGP Records
        - Funk Deluxe - Funk Deluxe, 1984; SR-15982; Funk Deluxe (Box 272)
          Catalog # SA 8565; A-side Matrix # SA-8565-A-1
        - Funk Solution - Black hoodoo, SR-15983; Funk Solution (Box 272)
          Catalog # FR 778; A-side Matrix # GIPSY HOODOO A
          Flying Records
        - Funk Masters - It's over, 1983; SR-15984; Funk Masters (Box 272)
          Catalog # JD-13638; A-side Matrix # PD-13638A-1
        - Funkadelic - You'll like it too; Long red, 2001; SR-15985; Funkadelic; Mountain (Box 272)
          Catalog # AO-9517; A-side Matrix # AO 9517 A
          Alpha Omega Recordings
        - Funkadelic - You'll like it too; Long red, 2001; SR-15986; Funkadelic; Mountain (Box 272)
        - Funkadelic - One nation under a groove, 1978; SR-15987; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          Catalog # BSK 3209; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3209 WW-2113AZ
        - Funkadelic - America eats its young (Disc one), 1972; SR-15988; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15989. Double album.
          Catalog # SEW2 029; A-side Matrix # DM D-4832A-1
        - Funkadelic - America eats its young (Disc two), 1972; SR-15989; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-15988. Double album.
          Catalog # SEW2 029; A-side Matrix # 005 DM D-4833-A1
        - Funkadelic - Standing on the verge of getting it on, 1974; SR-15990; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          Catalog # SEWA 040; A-side Matrix # 104 DM F-2886-A-1
        - Funkadelic - Maggot brain, 1990; SR-15991; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          Catalog # SEW 002; A-side Matrix # 007 DMC-7329 A-2
        - Funkadelic - The electric spanking of war babies, 1991; SR-15992; Funkadelic (Box 272)
          Catalog # P1 53874; A-side Matrix # P1-53874-A S-28336
          Priority Records
        - Funkaho - Villain style, 2003; SR-15993; Funkaho (Box 272)
          Catalog # STH 2073; A-side Matrix # STH-2073-A RE-1
          Stones Throw Records
        - Funkdoobiest - The funkiest; Freak mode, 1993; SR-15994; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # EAS 5240; A-side Matrix # XSS 5240B-1A
        - Funkdoobiest - Wopbabalubop; Where's it at, 1993; SR-15995; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # 49 77174; A-side Matrix # XSS 77174A-1A
        - Funkdoobiest - Bow wow wow, 1992; SR-15996; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # EAS 4969; A-side Matrix # XSS 4969-1A
        - Funkdoobiest - Freak mode, 1993; SR-15997; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # EAS 5240; A-side Matrix # XSS 77045B-1A
        - Funkdoobiest - XXX funk, 1995; SR-15998; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # AED 7291; A-side Matrix # XSS 7291A-1B
        - Funkdoobiest - Dedicated, 1995; SR-15999; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # 49 77915; A-side Matrix # XSS 77915A-1B
        - Funkdoobiest - Brothas doobie, 1995; SR-16000; Funkdoobiest (Box 272)
          Catalog # E 64195; A-side Matrix # AL-64195-2
        - Funke Fella - Git on up, 1998; SR-16001; Funke Fella (Box 272)
          Catalog # ASF0898; A-side Matrix # ASF-0898-A
          Asife Records
        - Funke Natives - Urban contemporary Jeep music; Warning, 1991; SR-16002; Funke Natives (Box 272)
          Catalog # AMI-002; A-side Matrix # AMI 002 A
          Amistad
        - Funkmaster Flex - C'mon baby; Butterfly style, 1993; SR-16003; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-16004; SR-16005. 2 copies; different discs.
          Catalog # NER 20065; A-side Matrix # NER 20065-A
          Wreck Records
        - Funkmaster Flex - C'mon baby; Butterfly style, 1993; SR-16004; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-16003; SR-16005. 2 copies; different discs.
        - Black Moon - How many emcee's (Must get dissed); Act like u want it, 1993; SR-16005; Black Moon (Box 272)
          In same jacket as # SR-16003; SR-16004. Different discs.
          Catalog # NER 20064; A-side Matrix # NE 20064-A
        - Funkmaster Flex - Dope on plastic, 1993; SR-16006; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          Catalog # MB 014; A-side Matrix # MB-014-A
          Massive B
        - Funkmaster Flex - Here we go, 1998; SR-16007; Funkmaster Flex; Khadejia (Box 272)
          Catalog # RDAB 65542; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65542-1-A1
          Loud Records
        - Funkmaster Flex - The mix tape vol. III sampler, 1998; SR-16008; Funkmaster Flex (Box 272)
          Catalog # RDAB 65656; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65656-1-A-1